<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cavedroid</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="shortcut_search">Item Search</string>
    <string name="shortcut_rankings">Rankings</string>

    <string name="home_balance_caption">Coins in account:</string>
    <string name="home_earnings_caption">Total earnings in market:</string>
    <string name="home_spendings_caption">Total spending in market:</string>
    <string name="home_sold_caption">Items sold:</string>
    <string name="home_bought_caption">Items bought:</string>
    <string name="home_offers_caption">Current offers:</string>

    <string name="search_view_hint">Player Name</string>
    <string name="name_dialog_title">Put in your ingame name</string>
    <string name="name_dialog_button">@android:string/ok</string>
    <string name="name_dialog_error">Invalid Name</string>
    <string name="name_history_fetching">Fetching Data…</string>
    <string name="name_history_title">Name History</string>

    <string name="topbar_title_items_sold">Items sold (highest amount)</string>
    <string name="topbar_title_items_bought">Items bought (highest amount)</string>
    <string name="topbar_title_offers">Current offers</string>
    <string name="topbar_title_richlist">Richlist</string>
    <string name="topbar_title_top_sellers">Top Sellers</string>
    <string name="topbar_title_top_items">Top Items</string>

    <string name="item_amount">%1$sx %2$s</string>
    <string name="item_price">%1$s\nCoins</string>
    <string name="ranking_entry">#%1$d</string>

    <string name="item_dialog_information1">Item</string>
    <string name="item_dialog_information2">Amount</string>
    <string name="item_dialog_information3">Price</string>
    <string name="item_dialog_information4">Per Item Price</string>

    <string name="item_dialog_button1">Search for Item</string>
    <string name="item_dialog_button2.1">View Buyer</string>
    <string name="item_dialog_button2.2">View Seller</string>
    <string name="item_dialog_button3">Copy Player Name</string>
    <string name="item_dialog_button4">Copy Item Name</string>
    <string name="item_dialog_button5">Copy Price</string>
    <string name="item_dialog_button6">Copy Per Item Price</string>

    <string name="item_search_hint">Search</string>

    <string name="item_search_dialog_information1">@string/item_dialog_information1</string>
    <string name="item_search_dialog_information2">Stack Size</string>
    <string name="item_search_dialog_information3">Total Price</string>
    <string name="item_search_dialog_information4">@string/item_dialog_information4</string>

    <string name="item_search_dialog_button1">View Seller Profile</string>
    <string name="item_search_dialog_button2">Copy Seller Name</string>
    <string name="item_search_dialog_button3">@string/item_dialog_button4</string>
    <string name="item_search_dialog_button4">@string/item_dialog_button5</string>
    <string name="item_search_dialog_button5">@string/item_dialog_button6</string>

    <string name="ranking_button1">Richlist</string>
    <string name="ranking_button2">Top Sellers</string>
    <string name="ranking_button3">Top Items</string>

    <string name="ranking_player_data1">%1$s\nCoins</string>
    <string name="ranking_player_data2">%1$s\nCoins Turnover</string>

    <string name="ranking_item_units">%1$s\nSold Units</string>
    <string name="ranking_item_turnover">%1$s\nCoins</string>

    <string name="ranking_player_dialog_button1">View Profile</string>
    <string name="ranking_player_dialog_button2">Copy Name</string>
    <string name="ranking_player_dialog_button3">Copy Balance</string>

    <string name="ranking_item_dialog_information1">Sold Units</string>
    <string name="ranking_item_dialog_information2">Total Turnover</string>
    <string name="ranking_item_dialog_information3">Per Item Average</string>

    <string name="ranking_item_dialog_button1">Search for Item</string>
    <string name="ranking_item_dialog_button2">Copy Item Name</string>
    <string name="ranking_item_dialog_button3">Copy Sold Units</string>
    <string name="ranking_item_dialog_button4">Copy Total Turnover</string>
    <string name="ranking_item_dialog_button5">Copy Per Item Price</string>

    <string name="clipboard_category_name">name</string>
    <string name="clipboard_category_item">item</string>
    <string name="clipboard_category_price">price</string>
    <string name="clipboard_category_per_item_price">per item price</string>
    <string name="clipboard_category_amount">amount</string>
    <string name="clipboard_category_turnover">turnover</string>

    <string name="about_icons_title">Used Icons</string>
    <string name="about_animations_description">%1$s animation by %2$s</string>

    <string name="feedback_dialog_title">Have some feedback?</string>
    <string name="feedback_dialog_message">If you have some feedback or you found a bug, feel free to report it on the GitHub repository.</string>
    <string name="feedback_dialog_button">Open Repo</string>

    <string name="missing_icons_dialog_title">Missing Icons Report</string>
    <string name="missing_icons_dialog_message1">%1$s missing icon(s) found.\n\nDo you want to report them to me (Cyb3rKo) including your
        name?</string>
    <string name="missing_icons_dialog_message2">No missing icons found.\n\nThere\'s nothing to report.</string>
    <string name="missing_icons_dialog_button">@android:string/ok</string>
    <string name="missing_icons_discord_message">----------\n%1$s, Missing Icons: %2$d\n</string>

    <string name="intro_fragment1_title">Welcome…</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment1_description">This is the unofficial Cavedroid app made by Cyb3rKo</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment2_title">Feel free to contribute</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment2_description">If you experience any problems or if you have a idea for a new feature, feel free to visit the GitHub
        repository and open an issue or a pull request.\nThanks!</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment3_title">End User Consent</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment3_description">For using this app you may agree to the Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment3_button1">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment3_check1">I agree to the Terms of Use.</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment3_button2">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment3_check2">I agree to the Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment3_toast">To continue you have to agree to both</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment4_title">Data Collection</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment4_description1">You can help me to (quickly) fix bugs and improve the app performance by allowing data collection
        (you can change them later in the settings):\n\n<u>Firebase Analytics</u>:\nProviding me with simple usage data mentioned in the Privacy
        Policy.</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment4_check1">I agree to data collection via Analytics.</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment4_description2"><u>Firebase Crashlytics</u>:\nProviding me with logs after this app crashes to fix the relating
        bugs.</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment4_check2">I agree to data collection via Crashlytics.</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment5_title">Ready…</string>
    <string name="intro_fragment5_description">OK, everything is set up.\nEnjoy!</string>

    <string name="end_user_consent_title">End User Consent</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_message">By using this app you agree to the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_button_1">Got it</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_button_2">Cancel</string>

    <string name="end_user_consent_2_title">Your End User Consent</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_2_message_1">By using this app you have agreed to the Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy.\n\nDate:&#160;</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_2_message_2">\n<u>Time:</u> </string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_2_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_2_terms_of_use">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_2_date">Date</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_2_time">Time</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_2_date_not_found">Date not found</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_2_time_not_found">Time not found</string>
    <string name="end_user_consent_2_button_2">Revoke</string>

    <string name="preferences_deletion_done">Deletion done</string>

    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_element_version">Version %1$s (%2$d) — Changelog</string>
    <string name="about_description">The Unofficial Mobile Client for the Cavetale Server</string>
    <string name="about_changelog_link" translatable="false">https://github.com/cyb3rko/cavedroid/releases</string>
    <string name="about_group_legal">Legal</string>
    <string name="about_element_libraries">Used Libraries</string>
    <string name="about_element_background_images">Used Background Images</string>
    <string name="about_element_icons">Used Icons</string>
    <string name="about_element_animations">Used Animations</string>
    <string name="about_group_connect">Connect with me</string>
    <string name="about_element_feedback_text">Visit and give feedback on GitHub</string>
    <string name="about_element_email_text">Contact me</string>
    <!--    <string name="about_element_website_value" translatable="false">https://cyb3rko.de</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="about_element_website_text">Visit my website</string>-->
    <string name="about_element_youtube_text">Watch my tutorial videos (in German)</string>
    <string name="about_element_github_text">Take a look at my other projects</string>
    <string name="about_element_instagram_text">Follow me</string>

    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making">https://cavetale.com/wiki/colorfall-map-making/</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making1"><![CDATA[*Originally written by feydk*\n\nIn its purest form, a Colorfall map is really simple to make. If you’re interested in making a map, you can buy a creative world for 10,000 Coins.\n\n ######Map rules\n \u2022 The Map must be built in a void world, since falling to the void is a fundamental part of the game. <br/> \u2022 The vertical center block should be somewhere around the Y 60 range. <br/> \u2022 All colored blocks must have a clear path downwards to the void. I.e. no block directly below a colored block.\n\n######Block palette\n \u2022 For the colored blocks, you can use any block that can be dyed/stained; wool, stained clay and stained glass. <br/> \u2022 For the other blocks, you can use any block you want, but it’s advised to use blocks with strong contrast to the colored blocks. Quartz blocks works pretty well in that aspect since they are almost pure white in most texture packs.\n\n######Map configuration\n When you make your map, pick one block for the colored blocks. That one block works as a placeholder, and it can be any block you like (it won’t show up in the game).\n\nSee the image below. The cyan wool blocks are the placeholders, which will be replaced when the game starts:]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making_link1">https://i.imgur.com/pyLx7Vtl.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making2"><![CDATA[To “tell the game“ what block is actually the placeholder block, you must place a placeholder block somewhere and put a sign on it with [BLOCK] in the first line, like so:]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making_link2">https://i.imgur.com/0WapOP4l.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making3"><![CDATA[The next thing you need to do is decide on the colors to use in the game. This is also done by putting signs on blocks, with the first line of the sign being [COLOR], like so:]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making_link3">https://i.imgur.com/ANT6YwSl.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making4"><![CDATA[As you can see, I picked the colors purple, lime, red, light blue and orange.\n\nHow does this all come together? Simple: <br/> \u2022 When the game loads, it searches for the placeholder blocks (the one you marked with [BLOCK]). <br/> \u2022 For every block it finds, it replaces it with a random colored block (the ones you marked with [COLOR]).\n\nFor the sample pictures I’ve used in this post, that means: <br/> \u2022 Every cyan wool block will be replaced by either a purple, lime, red, light blue or orange wool block.\n\n######Spawn locations\n So far so good. The next step is to mark locations where players can spawn. To mark a spawn location, put down a sign and put [SPAWN] in the first line, like so:]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making_link4">https://i.imgur.com/mcXzKhXl.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making5"><![CDATA[I recommend having some distance between spawn locations, and at least 8 of them, preferably 12–16.\n\n######Defining the map region\n If your map uses decoration “outside“ of the actual map, such as titles/logos or any other form of decoration that’s not part of the map you run around on, you should/must define the actual map region. The region is a cuboid, just like a world edit selection. You mark the two corners (upper point in one corner, lower point in the opposite corner) with [BOUNDARY] signs, like depicted below. There can only be two of these signs in a map. Any blocks outside the cuboid will not be removed during the game.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making_link5">https://i.imgur.com/xd18nOIl.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making6"><![CDATA[######Credits\n This step is optional. If you want to credit the builders of the map (which means you and any helpers you had), you can do that by putting up one or more signs, each having [CREDITS] in the first line. See the example below:]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making_link6">https://i.imgur.com/OuGi96xl.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making7"><![CDATA[Put one name per line. If you need more than 3 names, simply make more signs. The signs cannot be attached to other blocks with signs attached to them. If you use these credit signs, the name(s) on them will show up in chat when players join a game.\n\n######Time\n This step is optional. If you want, you can specify the starting time of the world when the game loads. Ie if it should bes day, night, dusk etc. Use a [TIME] sign to do that. On the second line you specify the time, and on the third line you can specify if the time should be locked:]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making_link7">https://i.imgur.com/CNVuXsyl.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_map_making8"><![CDATA[In the image above I set the time to 16000 (night time), and I want it to be locked. If you don’t want to lock time, simply leave out the third line. If you don’t care about time at all, leave out the entire sign. In which case the game will use the default settings.\n\n######And that is it!\n I hope some of you take up this challenge and start making maps so the game of Colorfall can be even more varied. If you do, be sure to let us know, and then we might actually use your map in the game.]]></string>

    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making">https://cavetale.com/wiki/vertigo-map-making/</string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making1"><![CDATA[*Originally written by feydk*\n\nIf you’re interested in making a map, your first step will be to purchase a new creative world for 10,000 coins.\n\nWhen making a map for Vertigo, there are some things you need to consider:\n\n \u2022 **The size of the pool.** The size determines how long the game will drag on for, if all players keep up with each other. So consider this carefully. If a couple of equally skilled players play a map with a pool of, say 15×15, it will take a considerable time to complete a game. For comparison, the default map uses a pool of 7×7.\n\n \u2022 **The jump height.** The higher up, the easier it becomes to move in the air, but it may also become more difficult to get a good aim. And don’t forget to take render distance into consideration as well. There is really no limit to the jump height. For comparison, the default map uses a jump height of 30 blocks (above the pool).\n\n \u2022 **The decoration and surroundings.** Basically, you can do what you want. You could make a colorful drop, an Olympic swimming stadium or whatever. But keep in mind there must be designated places for players to spawn, and there must be a way to spectate the jumps from below. Ideally players should have a clear view to the jumping platform from the spawn positions.\n\n \u2022 **And a few rules:** the drop area must be surrounded by barrier blocks or solid blocks so that you can’t jump “out”. The pool has to have water in it. Also check the relevant requirements in the sections below.\n\nBefore you start building, also consider the following requirements for map configuration, as they may have an impact on how you design your map.\n\n######Pool requirements\n Must be square. Must have exactly 2 [BOUNDARY] signs (see below). Must have one [water] sign (see below). Must be one block deep.\n\nThe bordering blocks around the pool must use a material different from the blocks that are used to fill up the pool. See “Pool filler blocks“.\n\n######Pool configuration signs\n You need to use 2 signs to define the opposite pool corners. Check out this image:]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making_link1">https://i.imgur.com/y53bGkel.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making2"><![CDATA[As you can see, this is the block below one of the pool corners. Attach a **[BOUNDARY]** sign to that block. Do the same for the block in the opposite corner, so that the signs define a cuboid for the pool. This is required to make golden ring spawning work. The signs are removed when the game starts. You also need to tell the game how much water there actually is in the pool. Do this simply by having a **[WATER]** sign with the exact number of water blocks on the second line. In this example it says 49, because the pool size is 7×7. This sign is removed when the game starts.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making_link2">https://i.imgur.com/DmlvKZll.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making3"><![CDATA[######Pool filler blocks\n As players drop into the water, the water blocks get replaced by solid blocks. You must define which blocks, using a chest:]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making_link3">https://i.imgur.com/oaAlALYl.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making4"><![CDATA[Name a chest called **[BLOCKS]** and put it somewhere. It is removed when the game starts. Put in the blocks you want to be filler blocks. The game will choose a random one from the chest every time a splash is made. You cannot use the block(s) used for the pool border.\n\n######Jump platform requirements\n You can make this pretty much any way you want, but you need to keep this in mind: every water block of the pool should be possible to reach when you jump off the platform. It doesn’t have to be a ring-formed platform like in the default map, you could also just have something like a diving board or similar. The platform does need to have some space so that players don’t involuntary fall if they are moving while being teleported to the platform.\n\n######Jump platform signs\n You must define the position(s) to which players are teleported when it’s their turn to jump, by having **[JUMP]** signs. You can have as many of these as you like (the default map has 4, as you can see in the image below). I would say there has to be at least 2 blocks in front of the sign, but not too many either, so that players don’t spend precious time getting to the edge.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making_link4">https://i.imgur.com/XQT6Usel.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making5"><![CDATA[The game needs to know how to determine if a player actually jumped. This is done by making a **[THRESHOLD]** sign. This sign needs to be placed as high as possible below the floor of the jump platform. If that doesn’t make sense, consider this:]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making_link5">https://i.imgur.com/VZH04TAl.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_vertigo_map_making6"><![CDATA[For reference, the chiseled block on top is the floor of the jump platform. If you use a single level jump platform, you can do the same as depicted. If you use a multi level jump platform, you have to find the lowest point and put the sign one block below. Don’t have too much of a vertical span between levels though, as that may affect the jumper’s ability to make the jump before time runs out.\n\n######Other configuration signs \nThe last requirement is to make **[SPAWN]** signs. I will refer to the Colorfall map making post on how to use these, as they work exactly the same in these two games. **[CREDITS]** and **[TIME]** signs also works the same as in Colorfall.\n\n######Testing your map\n Contact StarTux via Ticket.]]></string>

    <string name="wiki_world_edit">https://cavetale.com/wiki/worldedit/</string>

    <string name="wiki_landmarks">https://cavetale.com/wiki/landmarks/</string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks1"><![CDATA[On Cavetale, we regularly host week-long group build events. Exceptional builds are immortalized in the home world as **Landmarks**, where special Merchants sell unique items.\n\n#Locations\n \u2022 **Bazaar**]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks_link1">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/OverviewMain.jpg</string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks2"><![CDATA[ \u2022 **Witch Lair**]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks_link2">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/WitchLair.17.46-1024x576.jpg</string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks3"><![CDATA[ \u2022 **Dwarven Village**]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks_link3">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/5-HLfM7p4.png-1-1024x542.jpg</string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks4"><![CDATA[ \u2022 **Cloud Village**]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks_link4">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/CloudVillage-1024x548.jpg</string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks5"><![CDATA[Landmarks can be located on the Live Map (https://cavetale.com/map). They are marked by green flag icons.\n\nAlternatively, access them via **/warp**.\n\n#Merchants]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks_link5">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/LandmarkMerchant-1-1024x542.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_landmarks6"><![CDATA[In exchange for **Kitty Coins** (found uncommonly in Custom Dungeons (see *Custom Dungeons* in <u>Mining World</u>) and awarded during events), Merchants will offer a selection of custom gear themed to the Landmark they inhabit. These items have been given enchantments and/or attributes that are not normally available in the vanilla game.]]></string>

    <string name="wiki_link_portals">https://cavetale.com/wiki/link-portals/</string>
    <string name="wiki_link_portals_link1">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/0/04/LinkBetweenWorlds.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>
    <string name="wiki_link_portals1"><![CDATA[**Link Portals** are easy to construct, free to use links between any of our survival worlds. Every player may construct an unlimited number of these portals. The purpose of them is to make traveling from base to base easy and free of charge, whether the bases are in the same world or not.\n\n#Construction\n There are three different ways in which Link Portals can be constructed, each of which are listed here.\n\n##Basic portal\n 1) Make a Nether portal and light it. <br/> 2) Put a sign on the frame. <br/> 3) Write [link] in the first line. <br/> 4) Optional: put the name of the portal group in the second line. <br/> 5) Optional: use the third and fourth line for anything you want.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_link_portals_link2">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/5/5f/LinkPortalExample.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>
    <string name="wiki_link_portals2"><![CDATA[##Door portal\n 1) Make a 1×2 door-shaped frame with any solid block. <br/> 2) Put a sign on the frame <br/> 3) Write [link] on the first line. <br/> 4) Optional: put the name of the portal group in the second line. <br/> 5) Optional: use the third and fourth line for anything you want. <br/> 6) Place either a button or pressure plate inside of the frame to use the portal.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_link_portals_link3">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/a/a7/DoorPortals.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>
    <string name="wiki_link_portals3"><![CDATA[##Compact door portal\n Door portals are very flexible in how they can be made. The surrounding blocks can be in any position as long as the sign is above the triggering button or pressure plate. The side blocks can be removed to place multiple portals next to each other. Place buttons on the back wall to save space.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_link_portals_link4">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/9/9c/2016-02-21_22.37.41.png/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>
    <string name="wiki_link_portals4"><![CDATA[#Custom Nether Portals\n To ease construction of Nether portal-based Link Portals, you can make Nether portals of any size or shape. To do so, simply build the frame of the portal, put a sign in it, and write [Portal] in the first line.\n\n#How it works\n Link Portals are simple. All of your portals are connected with each other in a ring. Each player has their own set of portal rings, and it is not possible for one player to connect their portals to the ring of another player. One portal will take you to the next in line, in the order of their creation. You can have an unlimited amount of portals. You can have an unlimited amount of portal rings. Destroy a Link Portal by removing its sign. Portals can be created in all survival worlds, even in Resource or the Market.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_link_portals_link5">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/0/0c/LinkPortals.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>

    <string name="wiki_chest_shops">https://cavetale.com/wiki/chest-shops/</string>
    <string name="wiki_chest_shops_link1">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/c/c2/ShopChest.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>
    <string name="wiki_chest_shops1"><![CDATA[**Chest Shops** allow players to buy or sell items in exchange for coins.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/Shop List** - List transactions in your shop. <br/> \u2022 **/Shop Search [keyword…]** - Search the market for items matching either the item in your hand or the provided keywords. <br/> \u2022 **/Shop Search! [keyword…]** - Same as above, but display exact matches only. <br/> \u2022 **/Shop Sell [keyword]** - Search the market for items being bought by others. <br/> \u2022 **/Shop Search -owner [name]** - Search by shop owner. Lists deals only from that player. <br/> \u2022 **/Shop Port [owner]** - Warp to another player’s or your own shop.\n\n#Usage\n Open a shop chest to see what’s inside. A chest that wants you to buy things will read **[shop]** or **[buy]**. If it says **[sell]** instead, you are supposed to sell things to it. You always buy or sell whole slots of items. Each slot, with whatever stack size present, will cost the designated price.\n\nAll transactions are performed via **shift click**. To buy items from a chest, shift click them into your inventory. Each whole slot you take out of the chest costs the designated price. You have to buy the whole slot. You need to have enough money or it won’t work. The money will be taken from your account.\n\nA sell chest will allow you to sell any of the items that are already in the chest to it. The way this works is that whatever quantity of that item is in one slot of the chest, will be bought for the designated price. If there are different stack sizes of the same item type in the chest, the first one counts, starting from the top left. Items sold to a chest will be split accordingly, so the item stacks end up with the stack size that is accepted by the chest. The money will be transferred from the chest owner’s account to yours.\n\n#Sell items to players\n Looking at this from your customers’ perspectives, the sign should read “buy“, because that’s what they do: They buy things from your chest. Alternatively, it can say “shop“, since this is considered the default behavior of a shop chest.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_chest_shops_link2">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/a/a6/ShopSign.png/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>
    <string name="wiki_chest_shops2"><![CDATA[######Setup\n 1) Put down a chest. <br/> 2) Put a sign above the chest and write [shop] in the first line, and the price of your shopchest in the second line. Leave the other lines empty. <br/> 3) Put items in the chest.\n\nWhen every item in the chest has been sold, the price line on the sign changes to **“SOLD OUT“**.\n\n#Buy items from players\n Once again, look at this from your customers’ perspectives to realize that this type of chest must say “sell“, because they get to sell things to it. This type of chest requires you to put at least one slot of whatever people can sell to you in the chest.\n\nThe chest buys exactly what it can find in any of its slots, including amount, damage and enchantments, from any player for the price that is written on the sign. Items that are put in by people selling to you will not stack with the other contents, as to not make any changes to the setup, corrupting your shop chest.\n\nFor example, if you put 12 apples in the first slot and write 5 as the price on the sign, any customer can sell 12 or a multiple of 12 apples to the chest and will get 5 coins per 12 apples. The chest will be filled with slots containing stacks of 12 apples each.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_chest_shops_link3">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/2/21/SellSign.png/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>
    <string name="wiki_chest_shops3"><![CDATA[######Setup\n 1) Put down a chest. <br/> 2) Put a sign above the chest and write [sell] in the first line and the price you are willing to buy the items for in the second. Leave the other lines empty. <br/> 3) Put the items you want to be sold to the chest into it.\n\nWhen the chest is full, the price on the sign will change to **“SOLD OUT“**.\n\n#Signless Chest Shops\n Compact Chest Shops can also be created without using signs.\n\n 1) Rename the chest in an anvil with the format [shoptype] price. “[sell] 10“, for example. <br/> 2) Place the chest down. Optionally place another chest next to it to make a double chest. <br/> 3) Put the items you want to sell or buy into the chest.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_chest_shops_link4">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/4/41/Chest_Shop_Rename.png/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>

    <string name="wiki_titles">https://cavetale.com/wiki/titles/</string>

    <string name="wiki_ranks_staff">https://cavetale.com/wiki/ranks/</string>

    <string name="wiki_staff">https://cavetale.com/wiki/staff/</string>

    <string name="wiki_colorfall">https://cavetale.com/wiki/colorfall/</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_link1">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/4/4a/Colorfall-0.png/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall1"><![CDATA[**Colorfall** is a round-based party game, with an objective of hunting down and standing on specific colored blocks.\n\n#Command\n \u2022 **/colorfall** - Join an active game, or begin a new one.\n\n#Gameplay]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_link2">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/b/be/ClumpUp.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall2"><![CDATA[##Objective\nThe objective of Colorfall is to hunt down and stand on a specific colored block, which is specified at the beginning of each round. There are multiple blocks of the same color, so you must look carefully around the map to locate the correct ones.\n\n##Rounds\nThere are an unlimited number of rounds; the game will only end once all players but one are out of lives. At the end of each round, all blocks except for those of the specified color will disappear, and players in an incorrect location will fall to their doom. They will be able to re-join at the beginning of the next round.\n\n#Special Items\nSpecial items have a small chance of being granted at the beginning of each new round, and give their owners useful abilities in order to help them win the game.\n\n \u2022 **Clock** - Extend the round time by five seconds. <br/> \u2022 **Colored Dye** - Change the color of a block. <br/> \u2022 **Emerald** - Randomize some colored blocks. <br/> \u2022 **Feather** - Check if a block is the safe color of this round.]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_colorfall_link3">https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/7/73/Massive_Round_Started.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</string>

    <string name="wiki_enigmatica_6">https://cavetale.com/wiki/connect-to-ftb/</string>

    <string name="wiki_raid_hub">https://cavetale.com/wiki/raid-hub/</string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub1"><![CDATA[The **Raid Hub** is where players can access Cavetale’s many raid maps.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/raid** - Join the Raid server. <br/> \u2022 **/stash** or **/st** - Transfer gear and prizes between the Cavetale and Raid servers. <br/> \u2022 **/back** - Warp back to the previous checkpoint.\n\n#List of Raids\n ##2018\n **Advent Guardians** *by papamaci*\n\n**Bosses: 3**\n\n*The trio of guardians are keen to prevent the holiday season. Who will best them?*]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub_link1">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/2021-03-15_15.11.09.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub2"><![CDATA[##2019\n **A Thin Veil** *by Black0ut1*\n\n**Bosses: 3**\n\n*On Halloween night, the barrier between our world and theirs is at its most thin. At that time, you too shall perish.*]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub_link2">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/ThinVeil.jpg</string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub3"><![CDATA[**The Christmas Raid** *by killergames1, Koontzykinz, papamaci, MenoMano*\n\n**Bosses: 5**\n\n*Gather your friends, grab your best gear, fight through waves of enemies and find ways to defeat the dangerous beasts.*]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub_link3">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/2021-03-15_15.08.15.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub4"><![CDATA[##2020\n **Bunnies in Candyland** *by Black0ut1*\n\n**Bosses: 1**\n\n*The walls are made of cake!*]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub_link4">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/BunniesInCandyLand.jpg</string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub5"><![CDATA[**Mob Arena** *by Black0ut1*\n\n**Bosses: 5**\n\n*Fight through 50 waves of enemies, each tougher than the last.*]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub_link5">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/NewMobArena.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub6"><![CDATA[**Raider’s Mine** *by Black0ut1*\n\n**Bosses: 1**\n\n*Abandoned and unexplored for years, none can say what treasures lie at the end of the tunnel.*]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub_link6">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/2021-03-15_15.06.24.png</string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub7"><![CDATA[**Scary Halloween Show** *by Black0ut1*\n\n**Bosses: 3**\n\n*It’s showtime! Don’t you know that you’re the main event?*]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub_link7">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/ScaryHalloweenShow.jpg</string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub8"><![CDATA[##2021\n **Winter’s Edge** *by Black0ut1*\n\n**Bosses: 4**\n\n*The clacking of bones disturbs an otherwise serene silence.*]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub_link8">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/FrozenForestRaid-1024x576.jpg</string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub9"><![CDATA[**Castle Raid** *by Black0ut1, killergames1, Dupp*\n\n**Bosses: 2**\n\n*Fight amongst the flames to save the burning village.*]]></string>
    <string name="wiki_raid_hub_link9">https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/CastleRaidPromoSmallpng.png</string>
</resources>