<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="miniverse">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/miniverse/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-01-25</item>
        <item>Miniverse</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The **Miniverse** is a miniaturized version of the Beta overworld which allows for rapid travel. Each block in the Miniverse translates to **32 blocks horizontally**, and **8 blocks vertically**.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/switch** - Switch into or out of the Miniverse. (*Crouch* to exit the Miniverse.)]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Miniverse-1024x576.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="connect_to_beta">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/connect-to-beta/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-02-11</item>
        <item>Connect to Beta</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The **Beta server** is a test ground for plugin updates and new features. It may be rolled back or reset at any time.\n\n######Currently featured\n \u2022 **Skills Mk2** <br/> \u2022 **Quests**\n\n#Joining\n To join the Beta server, you must be ranked Member or above. See <u>Ranks</u> for details.\n\nOnce sufficiently ranked, use **/beta** to join the server.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Day_1.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="survival_games_map_making">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/survival-games-map-making/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-05-29</item>
        <item>Survival Games Map Making</item>
        <item><![CDATA[*Originally written by StarTux*\n\nSurvival Games maps are easy to make. All you need is a creative world. We recommend that you buy an empty (void) world. Bigger is better in this minigame.\n\n**Setup:** <br/> Place **chests** wherever you see fit. Chests near the world spawn (/world setspawn, within 20 blocks) are only stocked once, so they may be piled up. All chests must be empty!\n\nMake some **spawn signs:** Place a sign and write [spawn] in the first line. This is where players will spawn. It’s recommended to have at least 20 signs, placed in a circle around the spawn chests. More is better!\n\n**Optional**: Place some signs with [credits] in the first line around spawn, and write your names on it.\n\nThat is all! When done, make a ticket in your world and ask us to review it.]]></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="building_on_creative">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/world/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-05-07</item>
        <item>Building on Creative</item>
        <item><![CDATA[Having your own **World** to build in is essential to using the Creative server.\n\n#Command\n \u2022 **/World** - Open the World command menu\n\n#Obtaining a world\n To purchase a creative world, use the command **/world buy**. You will then be prompted to purchase a new world for 10,000 coins. Accepting will grant you a 256×256 area to build in. You may purchase as many worlds as you can afford.\n\nWhen purchasing a world, you may specify the world type you would like by adding the modifiers **flat** or **void** to the end of the buy command. If neither is specified, your world will default to void.\n\nOnce you have your world, you can spend money to unlock additional features with **/world unlock**. You can also expand your world with **/world grow**, which grows the border by 256 blocks in all directions for 10,000 coins.\n\n#Legacy plots\n If you had a plot in one of our past plot worlds, you may locate it via **/plot list**. Once located, use the **/plot warp #** command to be teleported directly there. While you may still build in your old plots, new ones are no longer available, and thus purchasing worlds will be required for future projects.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/BuyCreativeWorld-1024x542.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pocket_mob">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/pocket-mob/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-05-01</item>
        <item>Pocket Mob</item>
        <item><![CDATA[With **Pocket Mob**, players can capture mobs in Mob Catchers to ease their transport and be released elsewhere.\n\n#Purchasing Mob Catchers\n Mob Catcher items may be purchased at the pet store at spawn. The standard Mob Catcher ball may then be upgraded into one of five different specializations to improve relevant catch rates, which are:\n\n \u2022 **Animal Catcher** - which catches all animals within a radius. <br/> \u2022 **Monster Catcher** - which catches wounded monsters. <br/> \u2022 **Pet Catcher** - which catches mobs tamed by you, guaranteed. <br/> \u2022 **Villager Catcher** - which captures any villager. <br/> \u2022 **Fish Catcher** - which captures water mobs such as squid or fish.\n\n#Success rates\n While some captures are guaranteed (such as with tamed mobs), not every ball thrown has a 100% success rate. When it comes to capturing hostile mobs for instance, your success rate increases inversely with the monster’s health. Weakening monsters through combat and/or the use of potions before attempting to capture them is recommended to improve your odds at success.\n\nAnother factor to consider is your aim. More accurate throws will yield better results, so aim as close to your target as possible. When attempting to catch multiple mobs at once (such as in the case of the Animal Catcher), ensure that your targets are all within the catcher item’s radius.\n\nLastly, note that not all mobs may be captured. The use of Pocket Mob to steal the pets of other players or to grief is prohibited.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/PocketMob-1024x576.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="friendship">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/friendship/</item>
        <item>StarTux edited this page on 2021-09-24</item>
        <item>Friendship</item>
        <item><![CDATA[On Cavetale, sharing daily gifts will earn you **friendship points**. With enough friendship points, players have the opportunity to get **married**.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/friends** - View a list of players you have friendship points with. <br/> \u2022 **/friend &lt;player&gt;** - Send a friend request to a player (3+ hearts required). <br/> \u2022 **/profile** - View your profile\n\n#Building friendship\n ##Daily Gift\n Each day at midnight server time, a food item will be selected as the daily gift. It may be one of the following:\n\n \u2022 Apple <br/> \u2022 Cake <br/> \u2022 Cookie <br/> \u2022 Golden apple <br/> \u2022 Melon slice <br/> \u2022 Pumpkin pie <br/> \u2022 Sweet berries\n\nThrowing the daily gift to another player will increase your friendship with them. Each day that a gift is exchanged between you and another player, your friendship will grow and additional hearts will gradually be unlocked.\n\n##Events and Raids\n Participating in events (Saturday and Sunday) or defeating a raid together will also increase your friendship.\n\n#Friends\n Upon reaching a friendship level of three hearts with another player, you may send them a friend request with **/friend &lt;player&gt;**.\n\nFriends come with perks:\n\n \u2022 Never drop below two hearts <br/> \u2022 Starting a raid together with friends gives a health buff\n\n#Marriage\n Upon reaching five hearts of friendship with another player, you may propose to them.\n\nHead to the church at spawn (on your left after walking down the stairs towards the marketplace) to purchase a Wedding Ring from the merchant. Both players must have a wedding ring in order to get married.\n\nRight-click on your partner with your ring in hand to propose to them.\n\nOnce married, players may use **/love** to display hearts over their heads. Couples may also pick each other up by right-clicking them. Additionally, eating food near one another will nourish both players.\n\nIf in the future you and your spouse decide to go separate ways, you may use **/divorce** to break up.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/FriendsList2.png</item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Wedding-Ring-1024x542.png</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="slime_chunk_detector">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/slime-chunk-detector/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2020-03-11</item>
        <item>Slime Chunk Detector</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The **Slime Chunk Detector** allows you to search the depths of your claim for slime chunks.\n\nSimply head to y:40 or lower and right-click the ground with a slime ball in hand for immediate feedback.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/SlimeChunkDetector-3.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="market">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/market/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2018-10-27</item>
        <item>Market</item>
        <item><![CDATA[Cavetale has a central location where players can trade with each other called the **Market**. While shop creation is possible anywhere in the world, this is the place where people usually go to look for a bargain.\n\n#Commands\n There are a couple of commands to get around and find items on the market. The output of the search command is clickable, so you can be ported automatically if you see an item in the list that you are interested in.\n\n \u2022 **/market** or **/shop market** - Warp to the market spawn. <br/> \u2022 **/shop search [keyword]** - Search the market for items matching the item in your hand or the keywords. <br/> \u2022 **/shop search! [keyword]** - Same as above, but search for exact matches. <br/> \u2022 **/shop search -sell [keyword]** - Search the market for items being bought by others. <br/> \u2022 **/shop search -owner [name]** - Search by shop owner. Lists deals only from that player. <br/> \u2022 **/shop port [owner]** - Warp to someone’s shop, or your own shop. This is free of charge. <br/> \u2022 **/shop trust [player]** and **/shop untrust [player]** - Give someone else permission to build within your plot. <br/> \u2022 **/shop setspawn** - Set the spawn location of your plot.\n\n######Examples\n \u2022 **/shop search diamond pick** - Search for anything containing the words “diamond” and “pick”. <br/> \u2022 **/shop search! diamond** - Search for diamond items. <br/> \u2022 **/shop search -owner StarTux** - Lists what StarTux has for sale. <br/> \u2022 **/shop port** - Warp to your own shop. <br/> \u2022 **/shop port StarTux** - Warp to StarTux’ shop.\n\n#Location\n A whole world is dedicated to our market. You can reach it by typing **/market** or by following the appropriate portal at spawn. The market can be expanded on demand to the North and the South.\n\nThe market follows a canal that flows through its center. It is organized into four lanes, 2 of each side of the river, leading away from the market spawn in different directions. Each lane has an upper and a lower level.\n\n#Making a shop\n Main Article: <u>Chest Shops</u>\n\nOnce you have acquired adequate wealth and reached the Member rank, you can purchase a plot in the market for 5,000 Coins. To do so, find an empty plot, or use **/shop auto** to find one which has not yet been claimed. While standing in the plot you selected, type **/shop claim**. The plot is now yours and you can start building a shop.\n\nThere are two ways of making a shop chest to sell items. One uses a sign, the other uses a named chest. You can also make a chest that buys items from people. All these possibilities are detailed in the main article (see above).\n\n#Rules\n \u2022 Absolutely no griefing or stealing is tolerated on the marketplace. <br/> \u2022 Only build inside your own plot. <br/> \u2022 No buildings taller than 25 blocks are allowed. <br/> \u2022 No scamming. Make your offers fair and transparent. <br/> \u2022 Don’t use fire in your design. It is noisy and makes people lag. <br/> \u2022 No unnecessary towers which don’t contain shop chests.\n\nShops that violate the rules may be altered or removed at the staff team’s discretion. Whenever you are in doubt about the interpretation of the rules, feel free to ask a staff member for advice or assistance.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Market.png</item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/c/c2/ShopChest.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="datapacks">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/datapacks/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2020-12-05</item>
        <item>Datapacks</item>
        <item><![CDATA[Cavetale features several **datapacks** from the Vanilla Tweaks (https://vanillatweaks.net/picker/datapacks) series to give you more building and crafting options than you would normally have in the vanilla game.\n\n######Current datapcks:\n \u2022 AFK Display <br/> \u2022 Charcoal to Black Dye <br/> \u2022 Craftable Name Tags <br/> \u2022 Craftable Notch Apples <br/> \u2022 Dropper to Dispenser <br/> \u2022 Durability Ping <br/> \u2022 More Mob Heads <br/> \u2022 Uncraftable Ice <br/> \u2022 Uncraftable Nether Wart Block <br/> \u2022 Universal Dying <br/> \u2022 Wandering Trades]]></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="skills">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/skills/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2020-05-19</item>
        <item>Skills</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The **Skills** system allows you to collect skill points in several different categories. Certain activities will also grant you **Talent Points**, which can be used to unlock special abilities.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/sk** - Skills menu. <br/> \u2022 **/sk talent** - Unlock Talents. <br/> \u2022 **/sk hi** - Display the highscore.\n\n#Skills\n There are three skills with corresponding Talents: **Combat**, **Mining**, and **Farming**. They are progressed through the following actions:\n\n**Combat**: Fighting monsters.\n\n**Mining**: Mining ores.\n\n**Farming**: Harvesting fully grown watered crops (right-click crops with a stick).\n\n#Talent Points\n There are currently three ways to earn Talent Points: **Mining diamond ore**, **mining emerald ore**, and **harvesting fully grown watered crops**. Upon breaking each specified block, there is a chance for a Talent Point to be awarded. Each time the specified block is broken, the chance increases until a point is earned, at which time your progress to the next point resets. Once you have earned your first Talent Point, you may begin unlocking perks on the talent tree via **/sk talent**.\n\nNote that only watered crops that drop diamonds have a chance to award Talent Points.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/SKMining-1024x542.png</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mining_world">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/mining-world/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-09-08</item>
        <item>Mining World</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The resource world on the Cavetale server exists so people have a place to harvest materials from without having to worry about ruining the landscape or taking away valuable resources. This world, its nether, and its end dimensions are regularly reset with a brand new seed, so there is a constant supply of new resources. In this world, it is not possible to set homes or make claims.\n\n**DO NOT BUILD STRUCTURES OR LEAVE ITEMS HERE THAT YOU ARE NOT WILLING TO LOSE.**\n\n#Command\n There is a portal at spawn that will bring you to a random location in the resource world. If you want to pick where to go, use the command.\n\n \u2022 **/Mine** or **/Resource** - This command will give you a list of available biomes. Click the biome of your choice to be teleported there. This is free of charge.\n\n#Custom Dungeons\n During your time mining in the resource world, you may encounter **Custom Dungeons**. These are player-built structures that contain blocks and items superior to those found in vanilla dungeons. While custom dungeons may be randomly stumbled upon while adventuring underground, a surefire way to locate one is to **right-click with a compass in hand**. Depending on your depth underground, you will see a message in chat that either alerts you to dig deeper or notifies you that a dungeon has been located.\n\n#Restrictions\n Since this world has a special utility, other than the building worlds, a couple of restrictions apply.\n\n \u2022 You cannot set homes in this world. Use the **/Mine or /Resource** command to find the location of your choice. <br/> \u2022 You cannot make claims in this world. <br/> \u2022 There is no spawn location in this world. To go back ot another world, use **/Spawn** or any of your homes.]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/6/6e/Resource.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/CustomDungeon-1024x542.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="photos">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/photos/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2020-05-05</item>
        <item>Photos</item>
        <item><![CDATA[With Photos, you can import any image from the internet into the game, so it is visible to you and anyone else on a map. Photos can be viewed by holding the item, or by putting them on a wall for display. Creating photos is an opportunity to customize your build in a more personal way than the game would otherwise allow you.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/photo** - Open the photo menu which allows you to view and purchase more copies of your photos. <br/> \u2022 **/photo name [name]** - Create a photo with the given name. <br/> \u2022 **/photo load [url]** - Load a photo from the Internet onto the map in your hand. <br/> \u2022 **/photo color [color]** - Change the color of the photo.\n\n#Usage\n Photos are simple to use. There is one command: **/photo**, which will show you the main Photos menu. From this menu, you can purchase blank photos for 1,000 coins. For every blank photo, you can create one named photo, onto which you can then load an image from a URL. Here are the steps.\n\n 1) Buy a blank photo via **/photo** <br/> 2) Hold the new blank photo in your hand and load an image via **/photo load [url]** <br/> 3) Name the photo via **/photo name [name]** <br/> 4) View photo options at any time by right-clicking with one in hand. <br/> 5) Enjoy!\n\nSomething to keep in mind is that you have to supply the actual image link as the URL. If it doesn’t end on “.jpg” or “.png”, chances are that it is not a valid image and the loading won’t work. Another consideration is that some sites will deny the download attempt since it doesn’t come from a web browser. Your best bet is to reupload it to another site that does allow this. We recommend Imgur.\n\nYou can load another picture on the same photo if you change your mind later on. Just keep in mind that every existing copy of your photo will also change.\n\nLastly, photos always have a resolution of 128 x 128 pixels. If the imported photo is not of the same dimensions, it will be resized, so it is recommended to crop it into the right shape beforehand to avoid distortion. You can use applications such as Paint or Gimp to do so.\n\n*Please note that Photos are saved per-server, so the photos you create on the main server cannot be accessed on Creative, or vice versa.*\n\n#Rules\n Photos open up a whole new realm of possibilities in the game, so obviously there are also things we don’t like. Generally, your photo has to conform with server rules. If you display images which are offensive or obscene, you risk losing your photo. We reserve the right to delete any image we consider unfit. In an attempt to give you some guidelines of what is not allowed or frowned upon, here are some bullet points:\n\n \u2022 No offensive or provocative pictures <br/> \u2022 No images which are “not safe for work” <br/> \u2022 No copyright infringement <br/> \u2022 No advertising of anything outside this server]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/c/cf/PhotosTitle.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hopper_sorter">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/hopper-sorter/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2019-04-14</item>
        <item>Hopper Sorter</item>
        <item><![CDATA[Sorting items automatically became possible when hoppers were introduced to the game. However, the vanilla setup is space-consuming, expensive, and probably above the heads of many people new to redstone. The **Hopper Sorter** is designed to solve these problems.\n\n#Construction\n 1) Attach an item frame to a hopper. <br/> 2) Put an item in the item frame.\n\nWe like to call this construction a “Item Filter”. This hopper will only absorb items of the type in the frame. No other items will be allowed in. You can attach multiple item frames to all four sides of a hopper to make it accept any of the items contained therein.\n\n#Usage\n These item filters can be used for any number of redstone constructions, be it an item sorting system for your storage area, item detection for an elaborate slot machine or an item payment system. The items transported to your item filter can come from many different sources; the system will show the same behavior for all of them.\n\n \u2022 Dropped items on the ground, above the hopper. <br/> \u2022 Items transported above the hopper with a water stream. <br/> \u2022 Items from adjacent hoppers pointing at the item filter. <br/> \u2022 Items from containers above the hopper, including other hoppers. <br/> \u2022 Minecarts with chests or hoppers riding a rail above the hopper.\n\nAll of these would usually have their items transported into your hopper. Turned into a item filter by means of item frames, it will allow only the item types that are in one of the frames in the hopper. Use this system to have an item sorter that saves a lot of space, time, effort, and materials.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/ItemSorting.gif</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="armor_stand_editor">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/armor-stand-editor/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2018-09-30</item>
        <item>Armor Stand Editor</item>
        <item><![CDATA[#Using ArmorStandEditor\n\n 1) Hold the editing tool (default flint) in your main hand. <br/> 2) Left or right click away from an armor stand to open menu. <br/> 3) Select the labeled menu options. <br/> 4) Left click the armor stand with the edit tool in hand to apply those options. <br/> 5) Right click instead to edit in reverse!\n\nWatch the tutorial video here (https://youtu.be/8-kODSlNhtM)\n\n#Modifiers\n ##Axis\n The Colored Wool in the top left of the menu represents the x, y and z axis. These options do nothing by themselves but change how other options behave. For example, the Placement option will move the entire armor stand in a direction based on the chosen axis.\n\nA secret trick for cool people is that you can crouch and use the mouse scroll wheel while holding the edit tool to change Axis without opening the chest GUI! Please don’t tell anyone unless you think that they are cool.\n\nAffects body part Position and armor stand Placement modes.\n\n##Adjustment\n The Coarse Dirt and Sandstone icons represent Coarse and Fine adjustment. These options do nothing by themselves but change how other options behave. For example, the Placement option will the entire armor stand 1 block or 1/32nd of a block based on the chosen adjustment.\n\nAffects body part Position, Placement and Rotation modes.\n\n##Save Slots\n The numbered Flower icons represent Save Slot modes. These slots are used with the Copy mode to store information about the armor stand and the Paste mode to paste that information to another armor stand. There are 4 Save slots available from the menu. Additional slots 5–9 can only be accessed via command **/ase slot #**.\n\nAffects Copy and Paste modes.\n\n#Modes\n ##Rotate\n The Compass icon represents the Rotate mode. Left clicking an armor stand with this mode will rotate the entire armor stand clockwise. Right clicking will rotate the armor stand counter-clockwise.\n\nAffected by Adjustment. By default Coarse Adjustment rotates the armor stand 30 degrees and Fine Adjustment rotates the armor stand by 3 degrees. This is configurable in config.yml.\n\n##Placement\n The Minecart icon represents the Placement mode. Left clicking an armor stand with this mode will move the entire armor stand along the selected Axis. Right clicking will move the armor stand in the opposite direction.\n\nAffected by Adjustment. Coarse Adjustment will move the armor stand 1 block. Fine Adjustment will move the armor stand 1/32 of a block.\n\nAffected by Axis.\n\nTip: if you want to move the armor stand up, remember to disable gravity for that armor stand with the Gravity mode!\n\n##Position\n Leather Armor icons represent the Position modes. These modes control the position of the part of the body they represent. Left clicking an armor stand with this mode will move the selected body part in a direction determined by the selected Axis. Right clicking will move the body part in the opposite direction.\n\nAffected by Adjustment. Coarse Adjustment will move the armor stand 1 block. Fine Adjustment will move the armor stand 1/32 of a block.\n\nAffected by Axis.\n\n##Reset Pose\n The Lever icon represents the Reset Pose mode. Clicking the armor stand with the edit tool with this mode selected will reset all body part positions to 0. This will make the armor stand appear to be standing up perfectly straight.\n\n##Equipment\n The Chest icon represents the Equipment mode. Clicking the armor stand with the edit tool with this mode selected will open a chest GUI from which one may place or remove equipment to or from any equipment slot on the armor stand.\n\nThis enables the user to place things in slots that are not normally possible such as a diamond block on the head slot or a pumpkin or player head in either hand slot.\n\n##Show Arms\n The Stick icon on the right side of the menu (not to be confused with the stick icons near the leather armor!) represents the Show Arms mode. Clicking the armor stand with the edit tool with this mode selected will toggle the armor stand’s arms on or off.\n\n##Visibility\n The Potion icon represents the Visibility mode. Clicking the armor stand with the edit tool with this mode selected will toggle the armor stand’s visibility visible or invisible.\n\n##Gravity\n The Sand icon represents the Gravity mode. Clicking the armor stand with the edit tool with this mode selected will toggle the whether the armor stand will fall or not.\n\n##BasePlate\n The Stone Slab icon represents the BasePlate mode. Clicking the armor stand with the edit tool with this mode selected will toggle whether the armor stand will have a baseplate or not.\n\n##Copy\n The Book and Quill icon represents the Copy mode. Clicking an armor stand with the edit tool with this mode selected will copy the armor stand’s pose, visibility, gravity, baseplate and (only in creative mode) equipment. It does not copy the armor stand’s rotation. This copy will be stored in the selected Save Slot.\n\n##Paste\n The Written Book icon represents the Paste mode. Clicking an armor stand with the edit tool with this mode selected will paste stored pose, visibility, gravity, baseplate and (only in creative mode) equipment from the selected save slot to the armor stand.\n\n#Nametags\n Nametags in Minecraft allow players to name mobs that are special to them. However, Minecraft does not appropriately apply nametags to armor stands. This plugin fixes that and goes one step further!\n\nTo name an armor stand simply name a name tag on an anvil and then right click the armor stand with the name tag in hand.\n\nYou can also apply Formatting Codes to names by using the codes found here (https://minecraft.gamepedia.com/Formatting_codes) and replacing the § with &amp;.\n\n#Targeting\n Sometimes armor stands get in the way of other armor stands.\n\nTo alleviate this issue, we have the Targeting function. Simply press the “Swap Item in Hands” key (default F) while looking at the armor stand you wish to target. The target will glow for about 1 second. If the wrong armor stand was targeted, keep pressing F.\n\nThe Targeting function only works from a distance of about 10 blocks away. To untarget an armor stand, press the “Swap Item in Hands” key while not looking at any armor stands.]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/a/a4/Baby_creeper_wave.png</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="televator">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/televator/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2018-07-199</item>
        <item>Televator</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The **Televator** is a simple teleportation elevator that allow users to ascend or descend the floors of a building with ease.\n\n#Construction\n Televators are very easy to construct. Simply place two gold blocks on separate floors so that they align with one another. You may add more gold blocks to the Televator system as you see fit, but a minimum of two is required in order for it to function.\n\n#Usage\n To use a Televator, stand on one of the gold blocks that you have placed. In order to be teleported to the corresponding gold block, you may either jump to go up, or sneak to go down.\n\nNote that the Televator will not work if there are blocks in between the gold; the area between the gold blocks must be clear in order for the structure to function.]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/f/f3/Televator.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="magic_map">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/magic-map/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2019-01-03</item>
        <item>Magic Map</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The **Magic Map** is a custom navigation tool which will help you to explore the worlds of CaveTale.\n\n#Function\n When held in either hand, the Magic Map will follow the player as they travel around the world. It features several improvements over a standard map, displaying nearby players and claims in addition to the surrounding terrain. The Magic Map will also keep track of the world that the player is currently in, and will display cave systems if the player ventures underground.\n\n#Obtaining\n Each player is granted one Magic Map by default, but additional maps may be purchased from the shop at spawn for 50 coins.]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/c/cf/Mini_Map.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="economy">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/economy/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2019-04-15</item>
        <item>Economy</item>
        <item><![CDATA[On Cavetale, our currency is **Coins**. Players may earn coins through selling their valuable items.\n\nPlayers may start auctions for their precious items to sell them to the highest bidder. For a price, players may also claim a plot in the <u>market</u> to build a shop there, and sell items to other players that way. Lastly, you may sell your items to the bank at spawn or remotely via the **/sell** command.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/money** - Check your balance. <br/> \u2022 **/money send** - Send money to another player. <br/> \u2022 **/money top** - See the top 10 wealthiest players. <br/> \u2022 **/market** - Teleport to the market. <br/> \u2022 **/sell** - Sell items in your inventory.\n\n#The Market\n The Cavetale Market is where most transactions take place. It can be reached by using the **/market** command. The market consists of several unique shops run by players. Players with adequate wealth may claim a market plot via **/shop claim** and start building their own unique place of business.]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/e/e4/Kitty_Coin_Large.png/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mass_storage">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/mass-storage/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-09-08</item>
        <item>Mass Storage</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The **Mass Storage** system allows players to virtually store stackable items, which can be accessed at any time, from any survival world, via command.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/MS** - Open the Mass Storage menu. <br/> \u2022 **/MS List** - List the contents of your Mass Storage. <br/> \u2022 **/MS Auto** - Toggle automatic storage. <br/> \u2022 **/MS Dump** - Dump your inventory into storage. <br/> \u2022 **/MS [item]** - Withdraw the item which you have specified from your Mass Storage. <br/> \u2022 **/MS Search [item]** - Look up stored items. <br/> \u2022 **/MS Help** - Display a command synopsis. <br/> \u2022 **/MS Info** - Display a summary of what you have in storage.\n\n#Usage\n As stated in the opening paragraph, the Mass Storage system is intended to store stackable items that would otherwise cause clutter in your chests. As such, most non-stackable items, as well as items with extra data attached to them such as enchanted tools or armor, written books, filled shulker boxes, and potions cannot be stored using Mass Storage. The only exceptions are **saddles**, **boats**, **music discs**, **fireworks**, and **horse armor**.\n\nNote that inserting level 2 or 3 firework rockets will result in them being converted to level 1 when retrieved.]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/3/37/MassStorage.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="auctions">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/auctions/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2020-12-09</item>
        <item>Auctions</item>
        <item><![CDATA[With our auction system, you can have your precious items sold at a live auction to anyone online on the server. An auction goes for a set time after which the highest bidder automatically transfers you the money and receives the item or items.\n\nAuctions tend to be exciting and heated battles for the highest bid, depending of course on the offered item and amount of people on the server.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/auc** - Get information about whatever is currently going on with auctions. <br/> \u2022 **/auc ?** - See a command overview. <br/> \u2022 **/auc preview** - Shows the preview of the auctioned item. <br/> \u2022 **/auc hand [starting bid]** - Auction off the item in your hand. <br/> \u2022 **/auc start [starting bid]** - Be presented with a chest to put in the items you want to auction off. <br/> \u2022 **/auc history [id]** - Check the auction history. The gray items on the bottom are queued and will start later. Every auction has an id, which you can also supply as an argument to look up detailed information on a specific past or future auction. <br/> \u2022 **/auc end [minutes:seconds]** - End your current auction. The optional time parameter sets the remaining time formatted as **minutes:seconds**. <br/> \u2022 **/auc ignore** - Stop receiving auction information. <br/> \u2022 **/auc listen** - Automatically receive auction information again.\n\n#Getting Started\n The auction system has a couple of features in store. In order to not get lost, there are some helpful commands.\n\n######Commands\n \u2022 **/auc** - Get information about whatever is currently going on with auctions. <br/> \u2022 **/auc ?** - See a command overview.\n\n#Bidding on auctions\n To win the item which is up for auction, you have to attempt to place the highest bid. When the timer runs out, the highest bidder wins. The highest bid is not necessarily the price that the winner ends up paying, though. Instead, they pay just enough to beat everyone else. The minimum amount that you can bid is 10 coins above the current highest bid. Additionally, you have to overbid by at least 5% of the current winning bid. Bidding itself is free of charge.\n\n######Commands\n \u2022 **/auc info** - While an auction is going on, this shows you more information about it. <br/> \u2022 **/auc preview** - Shows the preview of the auctioned item. Helpful for player heads. <br/> \u2022 **/bid** - Place a bid.\n\n#Auctioning off items\n You can either auction off whatever is in your hand or put items in a virtual chest if you want to sell more than one stack of the exact same item (no different names, enchants or different numbers of uses left). In both cases, you can specify a starting bid if you want to start with anything other than the default of 50 coins. It is not advisory to start with a high bid, though, since starting low raises interest in the item and makes the price raise slowly. Starting an auction costs 50 coins. A starting price higher than 50 coins costs additional 5% of the starting bid. <br/> Your auction may not start immediately if there is already an auction going on. In that case, up to 5 auctions will be queued and start after the previous is finished. There is also a warm-up period of 5 seconds.\n\n######Commands\n \u2022 **/auc hand [starting bid]** - Auction off the item in your hand. <br/> \u2022 **/auc start [starting bid]** - Be presented with a chest to put in the items you want to auction off.\n\n#Check and control your auction\n There are many advanced commands. If your auction is not going as well as expected, you might want to shorten it or end it right away. If you are curious about past and future auctions, you can look up details. So in case you miss the end of an auction, you can still get information about it.\n\n######Commands\n \u2022 **/auc history [id]** - Check the auction history. The gray items on the bottom are queued and will start later. Every auction has an id, which you can also supply as an argument to look up detailed information on a specific past or future auction. <br/> \u2022 **/auc end [minutes:seconds]** - End your current auction. The optional time parameter sets the remaining time formatted as **minutes:seconds**.\n\n#Listen or ignore\n You will get information about ongoing auctions printed to your screen automatically. This can be distracting when you are not interested in the particular item that is being sold. Luckily, it is easy to turn the notifications off and on again.\n\n######Commands\n \u2022 **/auc ignore** - Stop receiving auction information. <br/> \u2022 **/auc listen** - Automatically receive auction information again.]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/3/3a/Auction.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="rules">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/rules/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2018-09-27</item>
        <item>Rules</item>
        <item><![CDATA[Reading, understanding, and agreeing with the rules is the only condition to join CaveTale. This is why you have to look at the rules before you can start playing. Violating a rule will usually result in a warning, ban, or other disciplinary measure, which will stay on your record.\n\n#Rules\n \u2022 Server language is English. <br/> \u2022 No griefing, stealing, or spamming. <br/> \u2022 No offensive skins, builds, or player names. <br/> \u2022 Treat other players with respect. <br/> \u2022 DO not take advantage of glitches. <br/> \u2022 No unfair mods or resource packs. <br/> \u2022 Do not cause unreasonable lag. <br/> \u2022 No advertising. <br/> \u2022 Do not use alternate accounts to gain additional claims or homes.\n\n#Guidelines\n \u2022 If you discover a bug, report it rather than taking advantage of it. <br/> \u2022 Try to keep some distance from other players builds. <br/> \u2022 Always claim your area before you start to build. <br/> \u2022 In case of abuse in chat, don’t feed the fire. Ignore and report the involved parties. “/ignore” and “/ticket” are your friends. <br/> \u2022 Follow the instructions of our staff members.]]></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chat">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/chat/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-09-08</item>
        <item>Chat</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The chat on Cavetale is organized into several channels, to separate what is talked about in your surroundings. Some of the channels allow players to speak with their friends, while others display server information.\n\nYou may join and leave each channel as you please. Additionally, you may focus on one chat channel at a time, which is where your messages will be displayed unless you specify otherwise.\n\n#Chat Channels\n Our chat system consists of six channels. You can listen to any number of them, but may only speak in one at a time. The channels are as follows:\n\n \u2022 **[G] Global chat** - Everyone can hear you. <br/> \u2022 **[L] Local chat** - Range limited by 500 blocks. <br/> \u2022 **[PM] Private chat** - Only the player you are messaging can hear you. <br/> \u2022 **[P] Party Chat** - Only players in your current party can hear you. <br/> \u2022 **[I] Information channel** - System log, join and leave messages.\n\nEach channel has a short abbreviation that you can use instead of the name. You must be in a channel to talk in it. To modify settings for a channel, use **/ch set** followed by the channel abbreviation. For example: **/ch set g**. Enter the command without a channel abbreviation to edit universal settings.\n\n#Commands\nChat settings <br/> In the chat menu (/ch), click on a channel to edit its settings.\n\nJoining and leaving channels, plus some additional features, can be done via commands. Like any other command, they start with a slash. Commands are very straightforward. You can replace the channel argument with either the name or the one letter shortcut of one of our chat channels.\n\n \u2022 **/ch** - Open the chat menu. <br/> \u2022 **/ch list** - See a list of available channels. <br/> \u2022 **/ch who [channel]** - See who is in the channel with you. <br/> \u2022 **/join &lt;channel&gt;** - Join a channel to read what people talk about. <br/> \u2022 **/leave &lt;channel&gt;** - Leave a channel to have some quiet. <br/> \u2022 **/&lt;channel&gt;** or **/ch &lt;channel&gt;** - Focus on a specified channel. For example, /g or /ch g to focus on Global.\n\n#Private Chat\n You can send private messages to other players and start private conversations that way.\n\n \u2022 **/msg &lt;player&gt; &lt;message…&gt;** - Send a private message to another player. <br/> \u2022 **/msg &lt;player&gt;** - Focus on the private conversation between you and another player. <br/> **/r &lt;message…&gt;** - Replay to the last person who messaged you. <br/> \u2022 **/r** - Focus on the private conversation between you and the last player who messaged you. <br/> **/ignore [player]** - Ignore or unignore another player, both in channels and private messages. Leaving out the player argument gives you a list of the players you are ignoring.\n\n#Party Chat\n You can create your own chat channels for you and your friends via party chat. All it takes is a made up party name that is known among your peers. You can only be in one party at a time.\n\n \u2022 **/party** - See which party you are in, if any, and who is with you. <br/> \u2022 **/party &lt;party&gt;** - Join or create a named party. <br/> \u2022 **/p &lt;message&gt;** - Talk in party chat. <br/> \u2022 **/p** - Focus your current party. <br/> **/party q** - Leave your current party. <br/> **/party invite &lt;player&gt;** - Invite someone to join your party. <br/> **/party accept** - Accept the invitation.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/WikiChat.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="home">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/home/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-09-22</item>
        <item>Home</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The home system allows you to set a number of home locations which you can later revisit. You have one default home, which you can visit any time free of charge, and an unlimited number of named homes that you can set inside of claims. You can invite people to individual homes, or even make one of your homes accessible to the public.\n\n#Commands\n Cavetale’s home system comes with a command interface, but all you need to remember is the command for the main menu, **/Homes** which will give you a list of all your other options, which you can click.\n\n \u2022 **/Homes** - Open the Homes Main Menu. All commands can be clicked on. <br/> \u2022 **/Homes list** or **/listhomes** - List all of your homes. <br/> **/Homes set [name]** - Set a home. <br/> **/Homes invite &lt;player&gt; [name]** - Invite a player to one of your homes. <br/> **/Homes public &lt;name&gt; [alias]** - Make a home public. <br/> **/Homes delete [name]** - Deletes a home.\n\n#Using your homes\n To use your own default home, use **/Sethome** to set it and **/Home** to visit. All of this is free of charge. Usually, you would set these at your main base as it is the place you will visit frequently.\n\n **/Sethome** <br/> **/Home**\n\nIf you would like to store additional locations, there are named homes. Setting a named home is free. <br/> In this example, you would set and visit a home named “mine”.\n\n **/Sethome mine** <br/> **/Home mine**\n\nIf you later wish to delete your home ‘mine’, use the following:\n\n **/Homes delete mine**\n\n#Inviting people\n Inviting other people to your homes is easy and free of charge. For example, this is how you would invite Notch to come and visit your default home, assuming it exists.\n\n **/Invitehome Notch**\n\nIf your friend is online, they will be notified that they were invited and can follow the invitation by clicking in chat. To find the invite later, they can simply list all invites.\n\n **/Homes invites**\n\nThey will find your name on their list and click it. Their default list will appear, which they can simply click to visit.\n\n##Invite to named home\n Let’s look at an example with a named home. You need to supply the name of your friend first, then the name of your home.\n\n \u2022 **/Sethome castle** <br/> \u2022 **/Homes invite Notch castle**\n\nYour friend would perform the exact same steps detailed above. Type **/ListInvites**, find your name on the list, then find the named invite. And of course, if they are online while you invited them, they will already have a clickable notification on their screen, no searching required.\n\nRetracting an invite is even easier than making one. Just get the list of invited people, then hit the edit button.\n\n **/Homes invites**\n\n##Public invite\n Sometimes it can be useful to grant every person on the server access to your home, say if you made a farm you want people to use. Sending out a public invite can be done as follows.\n\n \u2022 **/Sethome farm** <br/> \u2022 **/Homes public farm [alias]**\n\nYour home will then show up on everyone’s **/visit** list.\n\n#Restrictions\n \u2022 You cannot set a home within a claim that you aren’t trusted in. <br/> \u2022 You cannot visit any homes while riding a vehicle, such as a minecart or horse. <br/> \u2022 You cannot set a home in the <u>mining world</u>.]]></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="claims">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/claims/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-09-22</item>
        <item>Claims</item>
        <item><![CDATA[On Cavetale, you can claim land as your own to protect against malicious players trying to break your projects or steal from you. Claimed land allows the owner to build in peace without worry of other players building on it. Claim owners also have the ability to allow who gets to build on their land. A claim reaches from the build height all the way down to bedrock.\n\n#Commands\n All claim-related commands can be found by typing **/Claim**.\n\n \u2022 **/Claim** - List all primary claim commands. <br/> \u2022 **/Subclaim** - List all subclaim commands.\n\n#Creating your claim\n After finding a location in the home world to build (**/wild** helps with this), stand in the center of the area you’d like to claim and type **/claim new**. Your first claim is free and will have the dimensions of **128 x 128** blocks, and can be expanded later by purchasing claim blocks. Additional claims will begin at **32 x 32** blocks and cost **2000 coins**.\n\nOnce you have created a claim, you may allow your friends to build in your claim with **/claim trust &lt;player&gt;**. Other levels of trust include:\n\n \u2022 interact-trust - Use buttons and levers. <br/> \u2022 container-trust - Open chests and shear sheep. <br/> \u2022 co-owner-trust - Trust other players up to build (default) trust. <br/> \u2022 owner-trust - Do anything in the claim.\n\nIf you would like to invite players to visit your claim but not modify it, you can instead use **/claim invite &lt;player&gt;**. Visitors can interact with blocks such as doors and pressure plates by default, but not edit blocks. You can customize visitor permissions in the claim settings menu, **/claim set**.\n\n**REMEMBER TO NEVER ADD PLAYERS TO YOUR CLAIM WHO YOU DON’T KNOW. ONLY ALLOW PLAYERS THAT YOU TRUST TO BUILD WITHIN YOUR CLAIM AND ACCESS CHESTS.**\n\nNote that if you decide to abandon a claim at a later date (**/claim abandon** while standing inside its borders), your coins will not be refunded.\n\n#Claim Blocks\n The number of claim blocks you have determines how large your claim can be. In order to acquire more claim blocks, you must purchase them via **/claim buy [blocks]**. Claim blocks are sold at a rate of 10 blocks per coin.\n\nBy default, claims with unused claim blocks will expand automatically until they run out of blocks or contact another claim. You may disable this feature in the settings menu.\n\n#Subclaims\n Eventually, you may wish to divide your claim into smaller sections with unique permissions, such as for the purpose of creating plots in a town. To do so, see **/subclaim** for a list of relevant commands.\n\n The owner of the primary claim will also have ownership over any subclaims within its borders, but other players trusted in the primary claim will not automatically have access to subclaims. Subclaim permissions are unique and must be configured independently of the parent claim.]]></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="enderball">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/enderball/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-02-11</item>
        <item>Enderball</item>
        <item>**Enderball** is a soccer-like minigame. It is currently playable only during events.\n\n#Command\n \u2022 **/Enderball**\n\n#Gameplay\nAt the start of the game, players standing on the field are split into two teams: Red and Blue. Players outside of the field are considered spectators and are not assigned to a team.\n\nOne team is randomly selected to kick off, at which time the game begins. Each game of Enderball lasts for ten minutes.\n\nTo kick the ball, players can either:\n\n \u2022 **Left click** for a high ball. <![CDATA[<br/>]]> \u2022 **Right click** for a shallow ball.\n\nSprinting while kicking the ball will increase its distance.\n\nIf the ball is kicked out of bounds during play, the opposing team gets a short period of time for their throw in or corner kick.\n\nAt the end of ten minutes, the team with the most goals wins. If teams are tied, the game will end in a draw.</item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Enderball.png</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="king_of_the_ladder">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/king-of-the-ladder/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2018-10-12</item>
        <item>King of the Ladder</item>
        <item><![CDATA[**King of the Ladder** is a PvP-based game which pits players against each other as they attempt to break a block atop a tall ladder. The first to reach the top and break the block wins the prize!\n\n#Gameplay\nPlaying King of the Ladder is simple, even if it’s your first time.\n\n 1) Use **/KOTL** to warp to the arena. Sleeping in a bed once there is a good idea. <br/> 2) Once the block has been placed on top of the ladder, climb the ladder and try to break it. <br/> 3) You can hit and be hit by other players along the way to secure positioning. <br/> 4) The player who breaks the block at the top of the ladder wins, and the round ends.\n\n#Rules\n \u2022 No items besides food are allowed during the game, unless given to you by an admin. <br/> \u2022 Play the objective. Don’t start a brawl at the bottom of the ladder or attempt to ruin the fun in any other ways.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/KOTL.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="extreme_grass_growing">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/extreme-grass-growing/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2018-10-06</item>
        <item>Extreme Grass Growing</item>
        <item><![CDATA[**Extreme Grass Growing** is a casual game of chance that you can play with your friends. Unlike other minigames, Extreme Grass Growing is only available during special Staff-hosted events, so don’t miss out!\n\n#Command\n \u2022 **/EGG** - Teleport to the Extreme Grass Growing arena.\n\n#Gameplay\nExtreme Grass Growing events consist of several short rounds. Each works as follows:\n\n \u2022 Place a sign on a dirt block inside of the arena, and write your name on it. <br/> \u2022 After all signs have been placed, grass blocks will begin spawning randomly. This grass will spread to adjacent dirt. <br/> \u2022 Once the dirt block your sign is on gets covered in grass, you’re out. The last player whose sign remains on a dirt block wins a prize.]]></item>
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/2018-10-04_23.49.43.png</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="survival_games">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/survival-games/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-06-02</item>
        <item>Survival Games</item>
        <item><![CDATA[Survival Games is a PvP-based minigame where you collect loot from chests and try to survive longer than your opponents.\n\n#Gameplay\nThe game has several phases. Watch the timer in the sidebar to see what phase you are currently in and how long it will last.\n\n##Waiting for Players\nRight at the beginning, we wait for more players to join if they want to. This is your chance to invite your friends to join your game before it starts.\n\n##Peaceful\nAfter a brief countdown, a peaceful period starts where everyone can collect loot, with PvP disabled. Take this chance to gear up for the next phase, which is when PvP is enabled and people will try to kill each other.\n\n##Fight\nThis is the longest phase of the game. PvP is turned on and everybody is on their own. There are different strategies which apply here. You could try and play an offensive style to try and get your opponents out of the way as quickly as possible and collect their loot, thereby gaining an advantage over the remaining players. Or, you could play more defensive and avoid confrontations, thus stay alive and try to collect the best loot from chests. If only two people are left during this phase, they will get a compass which points to the other person left in the game, respectively.\n\n##Sudden Death\nIf the Fight phase ends without a winner, sudden death mode begins. In this phase, all remaining players will start at the spawn area, which they may not leave, and fight each other until only one player is left. The Wither potion effect is given to all players, making sure that they all will die eventually, bringing the game to its conclusion, with one winner, or a draw, where nobody wins.\n\n#Special Items\n##Flare\nThe flare is a firework rocket with a one time use per item. If you activate it via right-click, a signal flare will be launched above every person in the game, giving away their location. Use this item if you want to find out if other players are nearby, or where they are hiding.\n\n##Compass\nThis rare item will always point to the player closest to you. Use this tool to find people to kill, or run away from them to avoid getting killed. This item is automatically dealt to everyone if only two players are left in the game.\n\n##Land Mine\nThe Land Mine is a special item which you can lay on the ground as a trap. If a player steps on it, it will explode, killing them and everything around them. Be very careful when you see a land mine on the ground. You can disable a land mine by breaking it with your hands.]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/5/57/Survival_Games.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pvp_arena">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/pvp-arena/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2021-05-01</item>
        <item>PvP Arena</item>
        <item><![CDATA[**PvP Arena** is a minigame that allows players to fight their friends in intense battles using randomized gear and rule sets.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/pvparena** - Join or start a game of PvP Arena.\n\n#Gameplay\nAt the beginning of each round, players will spawn into the map with a randomized set of gear. Rounds may also feature a special rule set, which will be displayed on the top of the scoreboard on the right of your screen. Rule sets may shuffle players on kills, make arrows lethal, spawn zombie apocalypses, grant extra lives, and more.\n\nWhen only one player is left alive, their name will be announced on screen and the round will end. The game will automatically select a new map and rule set, and the next round will begin shortly.\n\nWhen you are finished playing, return to the main server with **/cavetale**.]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/f/f7/PvPArenas.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="vertigo">
        <item>https://cavetale.com/wiki/vertigo/</item>
        <item>Black0ut1 edited this page on 2020-05-19</item>
        <item>Vertigo</item>
        <item><![CDATA[**Vertigo** is a game of skill in which players compete to score points by jumping into a pool of water while avoiding obstacles.\n\n#Commands\n \u2022 **/vertigo** - Join an active game.\n\n#Gameplay\n\n##Objective\nThe objective of Vertigo is to score the highest number of points possible, by completing difficult jumps while attempting to land in a pool of water.\n\n##Rounds\nVertigo is played in rounds. Every player will be given the opportunity to jump once each round. In addition, a gold ring has a chance of spawning at the beginning of each new round, which will award bonus points to the player who passes through it and splashes successfully.\n\n##Scoring\nThe points that are earned after a jump are calculated based upon the situation that you landed in:\n\n \u2022 1 point is earned for splashing. <br/> \u2022 1 point is earned for passing through a golden ring and splatting. <br/> \u2022 1 point is earned for each adjacent block that you splash next to. <br/> \u2022 3 points are added to your splash score if you pass through a golden ring.\n\nAfter a player has scored, a block with their head on it will be left in the spot where they landed. Hitting this block will result in a splat.\n\n##Winning\nThere are two different ways to win a game of Vertigo. In order to win, a player must either:\n\n \u2022 Have the most total points when the pool has been completely emptied of water. <br/> \u2022 Take a 10 point lead over second place at any time during the game.]]></item>
        <item>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/winthier/images/5/51/Vertigo.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/1000</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>